I believe it was March of and me and my brother encountered a man named Aaron Dunn in Elk
Grove CA.
Now it was just a regular day I was about years old at the time and my brother was about
or anyways we come back home from playing basketball and my mum tells me and my brother
she needs a few items from the store me and my brother didn't hesitate we loved going
to the store because my mum usually would give us a bill and we could get whatever we
wanted so we're walking through the parking lot of the plaza where the store was we were
approached by a man that looked really pissed off and amped up he pulled up on us pretty
fast too like he didn't want us to leave he pulls in front of us and asks us hey how old
are you guys me and my brother not knowing what he was talking about we thought he was
a nutcase answered and he told me and my brother never let a woman hurt you and stay
in school and he drives off really fast so me and my brother are kind of shocked like
what the hell was that unbeknownst to all us he ended up shooting people at the Chili's
right across the street where the store was he was caught and sentenced to death in but
he'll never forget that day I knew he wanted somebody to shoot but we were too young he's
seen that wouldn't have been right but that's just one story in my life that has happened